<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<Song>
		<id>43662</id>
		<songbook_id>21</songbook_id>
		<title>Z - Psalm 103 (ESV)</title>
		<copyright></copyright>
		<created>2011-11-18 00:44:23</created>
		<modified>2011-11-19 23:54:21</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<active>1</active>
		<ccli_required>0</ccli_required>
		<amazon_links></amazon_links>
	</Song>
	<Arrangement>
		<id>47015</id>
		<song_id>43662</song_id>
		<description>Initial arrangement</description>
		<text>Leader: 
Bless the LORD, O my soul,
And all that is within me, bless his holy name!

All: 
Bless the LORD, O my soul, 
And forget not all his benefits,

Leader: 
Who forgives all your iniquity, who heals all your diseases,

All: 
Who redeems your life from the pit, 
Who crowns you with steadfast love and mercy,
Who satisfies you with good 
So that your youth is renewed like the eagle's.

Leader: 
The LORD works righteousness and justice 
For all who are oppressed.

All: 
He made known his ways to Moses, 
His acts to the people of Israel.

Leader: 
The LORD is merciful and gracious, 
Slow to anger and abounding in steadfast love.

All: 
He will not always chide, 
Nor will he keep his anger forever.
He does not deal with us according to our sins,
Nor repay us according to our iniquities.

Leader: 
For as high as the heavens are above the earth,
So great is his steadfast love toward those who fear him;

All: 
As far as the east is from the west,
So far does he remove our transgressions from us.

Leader: 
As a father shows compassion to his children,
So the LORD shows compassion to those who fear him.

All: 
For he knows our frame; he remembers that we are dust.

{new_page}
Leader: 
As for man, his days are like grass; 
He flourishes like a flower of the field;
For the wind passes over it, and it is gone, 
And its place knows it no more.

All: 
But the steadfast love of the LORD 
Is from everlasting to everlasting on those who fear him, 
And his righteousness to children's children,
To those who keep his covenant 
And remember to do his commandments.

Leader: 
The LORD has established his throne in the heavens,
And his kingdom rules over all.

Everyone: 
Bless the LORD, O you his angels,
You mighty ones who do his word, 
Obeying the voice of his word!
Bless the LORD, all his hosts, his ministers, who do his will!
Bless the LORD, all his works, in all places of his dominion.
Bless the LORD, O my soul!
</text>
		<searchtext>leader bless the lord o my soul and all that is within me bless his holy name all bless the lord o my soul and forget not all his benefits leader who forgives all your iniquity who heals all your diseases all who redeems your life from the pit who crowns you with steadfast love and mercy who satisfies you with good so that your youth is renewed like the eagles leader the lord works righteousness and justice for all who are oppressed all he made known his ways to moses his acts to the people of israel leader the lord is merciful and gracious slow to anger and abounding in steadfast love all he will not always chide nor will he keep his anger forever he does not deal with us according to our sins nor repay us according to our iniquities leader for as high as the heavens are above the earth so great is his steadfast love toward those who fear him all as far as the east is from the west so far does he remove our transgressions from us leader as a father shows compassion to his children so the lord shows compassion to those who fear him all for he knows our frame he remembers that we are dust leader as for man his days are like grass he flourishes like a flower of the field for the wind passes over it and it is gone and its place knows it no more all but the steadfast love of the lord is from everlasting to everlasting on those who fear him and his righteousness to childrens children to those who keep his covenant and remember to do his commandments leader the lord has established his throne in the heavens and his kingdom rules over all everyone bless the lord o you his angels you mighty ones who do his word obeying the voice of his word bless the lord all his hosts his ministers who do his will bless the lord all his works in all places of his dominion bless the lord o my soul </searchtext>
		<primary>1</primary>
		<key>A</key>
		<time_signature></time_signature>
		<bpm></bpm>
		<tempo>Slow</tempo>
		<created>2011-11-18 00:44:23</created>
		<modified>2011-11-19 23:54:21</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<ccli></ccli>
		<album></album>
		<font_size>16</font_size>
	</Arrangement>
</data>

