<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<Song>
		<id>35755</id>
		<songbook_id>21</songbook_id>
		<title>Better Than Life</title>
		<copyright>Cindy Cruse-Ratcliff | Israel Houghton © 2001 Integrity's Praise! Music | My Other Publishing Company | Lakewood Ministries Music | (Admin. by Integrity's Praise! Music) | (Admin. by Integrity Music, Inc.)</copyright>
		<created>2010-10-05 00:07:48</created>
		<modified>2010-10-05 10:29:30</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<active>1</active>
		<ccli_required>0</ccli_required>
		<amazon_links></amazon_links>
	</Song>
	<Arrangement>
		<id>38265</id>
		<song_id>35755</song_id>
		<description>Initial arrangement</description>
		<text>Verse 1: 
Your l[C5]ove is everlasting, it's an everlasting love [F/C] 
Your m[C5]ercy is as new as ev'ry rising of the sun [F/C] 
And Your l[Bb2]ovingkindness
L[F/A]ovingkindness is better than l[C5]ife [F5   C5   Bb2] 
Your g[C5]race is all sufficient, it's an all sufficient grace [F/C]
Your p[C5]ower and Your glory are for[C5]ever on display
And Your l[Bb2]ovingkindness
L[F/A]ovingkindness is better than l[C5]ife  [F5   C5] 

Chorus 1: 
Oh [G    F]      it's b[C]etter
Oh  [G]    bett[F]er than l[C]ife
Oh   [G]  so m[F]uch b[Am]etter
J[D7]esus Your lovingkindn[F]ess  [Bb6/9] 
Is better than l[C5]ife  [F5   C5   Bb2   C5   F5   C5   Bb2] 
                        [C] [(To Bridge)] 
Verse 2: 
F[C5]airest of ten thousan, of ten thousand You are fair [F/C] 
And n[C5]othing in this world could ever measure or compare [F/C] 
To Your l[Bb2]ovingkindness
L[F/A]ovingkindness is better than l[C5]ife [F5   C5   Bb2] 
[C5]All Your ways are just oh Lord, you're just in all Your ways [F/C] 
And [C5]I will lift my hands oh Lord with gr[C5]atitude and praise
For Your l[Bb2]ovingkindness
L[F/A]ovingkindness is better than l[C5]ife  [F5   C5] 

{new_page}
BRIDGE: 
[C]   So we lift up our hands  [DM7] 
And we lift up our voices to t[C/E]estify
[F]   You are good
[F/G]    You are better than life
[C]   So we lift up our hands  [DM7] 
And we lift up our voices to t[C/E]estify
[F]   That's why we s[F/G]ing Jesus
[C]Je-[Dm7]sus Your loving[C/E]kind-n[Am]ess
Is better than [Dm]life itself
Better than l[F]ife its[G]elf
[C]Je-[Dm7]sus Your loving[C/E]kind-n[Am]ess
Is better than [Dm]life its[F]elf
[G]  Is better than l[C5]ife  [F5   C5] 

ENDING: 
J[D7]esus, your lovingk[F]indness  [Bb9] 
Better than l[C5]ife  [F5   C5   Bb2] 
Better than l[C5]ife  [F5   C5   Bb2] 
Better than l[C5]ife  [F5   C5   Bb2    C] </text>
		<searchtext>verse 1 your love is everlasting its an everlasting love your mercy is as new as evry rising of the sun and your lovingkindness lovingkindness is better than life your grace is all sufficient its an all sufficient grace your power and your glory are forever on display and your lovingkindness lovingkindness is better than life chorus 1 oh its better oh better than life oh so much better jesus your lovingkindness is better than life verse 2 fairest of ten thousan of ten thousand you are fair and nothing in this world could ever measure or compare to your lovingkindness lovingkindness is better than life all your ways are just oh lord youre just in all your ways and i will lift my hands oh lord with gratitude and praise for your lovingkindness lovingkindness is better than life bridge so we lift up our hands and we lift up our voices to testify you are good you are better than life so we lift up our hands and we lift up our voices to testify thats why we sing jesus jesus your lovingkindness is better than life itself better than life itself jesus your lovingkindness is better than life itself is better than life ending jesus your lovingkindness better than life better than life better than life </searchtext>
		<primary>1</primary>
		<key>C</key>
		<time_signature>4/4</time_signature>
		<bpm>96</bpm>
		<tempo>Fast</tempo>
		<created>2010-10-05 00:07:48</created>
		<modified>2010-10-05 10:29:30</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<ccli>4042482</ccli>
		<album></album>
		<font_size>14</font_size>
	</Arrangement>
</data>

