<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<Song>
		<id>72190</id>
		<songbook_id>21</songbook_id>
		<title>He is Our God</title>
		<copyright>Jon Althoff, Bob Kauflin</copyright>
		<created>2017-10-16 17:29:23</created>
		<modified>2017-10-16 17:29:23</modified>
		<creator>23187</creator>
		<active>1</active>
		<ccli_required>0</ccli_required>
		<amazon_links></amazon_links>
	</Song>
	<Arrangement>
		<id>79788</id>
		<song_id>72190</song_id>
		<description>Initial arrangement</description>
		<text>[INTRO  Bb      | Bb       | Eb       | Eb (2x)]

VERSE 1:
[Bb]Who can light the fires of a thousand burning suns
[Bb]Blazing in the heavens? There is only One, He is [Eb]our God  [|  Eb]

VERSE 2:
[Bb]Who commands the nations, building up and tearing down
[Bb]Silencing His rivals? There is only One
He is [Eb]our God, [|  Eb]       He is [Bb]our God  [|  Bb]

CHORUS 1:
[Bb]Holy, You alone are [Eb]holy, matchless in Your [F]glory, [Eb]Holy God [&lt;i&gt;Intro 1x&lt;/i&gt;]

VERSE 3:
[Bb]Who would come to save us when we turned away His love
[Bb]Conquer us with kindness? There is only One
He is [Eb]our God, [|  Eb]       He is [Bb]our God  [|  Bb]

CHORUS 2:
[Bb]Holy, You alone are [Eb]holy, matchless in Your [F]glorly, [Eb]No one is like You
[Bb]Worthy, You alone are [Eb]worthy, we adore You [F]only, [Eb]Holy God [Bb        | Bb]

BRIDGE:
[Cm7]  Now to the King on the throne [Bb/D]  who was and is to come
[Eb]  And to the Lamb who was s[Gm]lain be g[F]lory

</text>
		<searchtext> verse 1 who can light the fires of a thousand burning suns blazing in the heavens there is only one he is our god verse 2 who commands the nations building up and tearing down silencing his rivals there is only one he is our god he is our god chorus 1 holy you alone are holy matchless in your glory holy god verse 3 who would come to save us when we turned away his love conquer us with kindness there is only one he is our god he is our god chorus 2 holy you alone are holy matchless in your glorly no one is like you worthy you alone are worthy we adore you only holy god bridge now to the king on the throne who was and is to come and to the lamb who was slain be glory </searchtext>
		<primary>1</primary>
		<key>Bb</key>
		<time_signature>4/4</time_signature>
		<bpm></bpm>
		<tempo>Medium</tempo>
		<created>2017-10-16 17:29:23</created>
		<modified>2017-10-16 17:29:23</modified>
		<creator>23187</creator>
		<ccli></ccli>
		<album>Prayers of the Saints </album>
		<font_size>13</font_size>
	</Arrangement>
</data>

