<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<Song>
		<id>69488</id>
		<songbook_id>21</songbook_id>
		<title>Z - Psalm 27:7-14 [ESV]</title>
		<copyright></copyright>
		<created>2017-01-13 07:53:28</created>
		<modified>2017-01-13 07:53:28</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<active>1</active>
		<ccli_required>0</ccli_required>
		<amazon_links></amazon_links>
	</Song>
	<Arrangement>
		<id>76652</id>
		<song_id>69488</song_id>
		<description>Initial arrangement</description>
		<text>Hear, O LORD, when I cry aloud;
  be gracious to me and answer me!
 You have said, “Seek my face.”
 My heart says to you,
  “Your face, LORD, do I seek.”
 Hide not your face from me.
 Turn not your servant away in anger,
  O you who have been my help.
 Cast me not off; forsake me not,
  O God of my salvation!
 For my father and my mother have forsaken me,
  but the LORD will take me in.
 
 Teach me your way, O LORD,
  and lead me on a level path
  because of my enemies.
 Give me not up to the will of my adversaries;
  for false witnesses have risen against me,
  and they breathe out violence.
 
 I believe that I shall look upon the goodness of the LORD
  in the land of the living!
 Wait for the LORD;
  be strong, and let your heart take courage;
  wait for the LORD!</text>
		<searchtext>hear o lord when i cry aloud be gracious to me and answer me you have said seek my face my heart says to you your face lord do i seek hide not your face from me turn not your servant away in anger o you who have been my help cast me not off forsake me not o god of my salvation for my father and my mother have forsaken me but the lord will take me in teach me your way o lord and lead me on a level path because of my enemies give me not up to the will of my adversaries for false witnesses have risen against me and they breathe out violence i believe that i shall look upon the goodness of the lord in the land of the living wait for the lord be strong and let your heart take courage wait for the lord</searchtext>
		<primary>1</primary>
		<key>A</key>
		<time_signature></time_signature>
		<bpm></bpm>
		<tempo>Slow</tempo>
		<created>2017-01-13 07:53:28</created>
		<modified>2017-01-13 07:53:28</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<ccli></ccli>
		<album></album>
		<font_size>16</font_size>
	</Arrangement>
</data>

