<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<Song>
		<id>43762</id>
		<songbook_id>21</songbook_id>
		<title>Z - Isaiah 9:2-3, 6-7 (ESV)</title>
		<copyright></copyright>
		<created>2011-11-25 15:36:07</created>
		<modified>2016-12-14 23:56:21</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<active>1</active>
		<ccli_required>0</ccli_required>
		<amazon_links></amazon_links>
	</Song>
	<Arrangement>
		<id>47120</id>
		<song_id>43762</song_id>
		<description>Initial arrangement</description>
		<text>WT Ladies: 
The people who walked in darkness
      have seen a great light;
Those who dwelt in a land of deep darkness,
      on them has light shone.
You have multiplied the nation;
      you have increased its joy;
They rejoice before you
      as with joy at the harvest,
As they are glad when they divide the spoil.
	

Congregation:
For to us a child is born,
      to us a son is given;
And the government shall be upon his shoulder,
      and his name shall be called
Wonderful Counselor, Mighty God,
      Everlasting Father, Prince of Peace.
Of the increase of his government and of peace
      there will be no end,
on the throne of David and over his kingdom,
      to establish it and to uphold it
with justice and with righteousness
      from this time forth and forevermore.
The zeal of the LORD of hosts will do this.

</text>
		<searchtext>wt ladies the people who walked in darkness have seen a great light those who dwelt in a land of deep darkness on them has light shone you have multiplied the nation you have increased its joy they rejoice before you as with joy at the harvest as they are glad when they divide the spoil congregation for to us a child is born to us a son is given and the government shall be upon his shoulder and his name shall be called wonderful counselor mighty god everlasting father prince of peace of the increase of his government and of peace there will be no end on the throne of david and over his kingdom to establish it and to uphold it with justice and with righteousness from this time forth and forevermore the zeal of the lord of hosts will do this </searchtext>
		<primary>1</primary>
		<key>A</key>
		<time_signature></time_signature>
		<bpm></bpm>
		<tempo>Slow</tempo>
		<created>2011-11-25 15:36:07</created>
		<modified>2016-12-14 23:56:21</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<ccli></ccli>
		<album></album>
		<font_size>18</font_size>
	</Arrangement>
</data>

