<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<Song>
		<id>50675</id>
		<songbook_id>21</songbook_id>
		<title>Z - Luke 2:8-14 (ESV)</title>
		<copyright></copyright>
		<created>2012-12-20 17:22:17</created>
		<modified>2013-12-21 17:28:49</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<active>1</active>
		<ccli_required>0</ccli_required>
		<amazon_links></amazon_links>
	</Song>
	<Arrangement>
		<id>54898</id>
		<song_id>50675</song_id>
		<description>Initial arrangement</description>
		<text>Aaron:
And in the same region 
There were shepherds out in the field, 
keeping watch over their flock by night. 
And an angel of the Lord appeared to them, 
and the glory of the Lord shone around them, 
and they were filled with great fear. 
And the angel said to them, 
“Fear not, for behold, I bring you good news 
of great joy that will be for all the people. 
For unto you is born this day in the city of David 
a Savior, who is Christ the Lord. 
And this will be a sign for you: 
you will find a baby wrapped 
in swaddling cloths and lying in a manger.” 


Aaron, Tim, Eric: 
And suddenly there was with the angel 
a multitude of the heavenly host praising God and saying, 
“Glory to God in the highest,  
and on earth peace among those with whom he is pleased!”</text>
		<searchtext>aaron and in the same region there were shepherds out in the field keeping watch over their flock by night and an angel of the lord appeared to them and the glory of the lord shone around them and they were filled with great fear and the angel said to them fear not for behold i bring you good news of great joy that will be for all the people for unto you is born this day in the city of david a savior who is christ the lord and this will be a sign for you you will find a baby wrapped in swaddling cloths and lying in a manger aaron tim eric and suddenly there was with the angel a multitude of the heavenly host praising god and saying glory to god in the highest and on earth peace among those with whom he is pleased</searchtext>
		<primary>1</primary>
		<key>A</key>
		<time_signature></time_signature>
		<bpm></bpm>
		<tempo>Slow</tempo>
		<created>2012-12-20 17:22:17</created>
		<modified>2013-12-21 17:28:49</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<ccli></ccli>
		<album></album>
		<font_size>14</font_size>
	</Arrangement>
</data>

