<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<Song>
		<id>35405</id>
		<songbook_id>21</songbook_id>
		<title>Z - Valley of Vision Prayer: Reproofs</title>
		<copyright>From “Reproofs” in The Valley of Vision: Puritan Prayers and Devotions, © The Banner of Truth Trust 1975.</copyright>
		<created>2010-08-12 00:26:21</created>
		<modified>2010-08-12 00:46:08</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<active>1</active>
		<ccli_required>0</ccli_required>
		<amazon_links></amazon_links>
	</Song>
	<Arrangement>
		<id>37851</id>
		<song_id>35405</song_id>
		<description>Initial arrangement</description>
		<text>A Prayer for Correction


O Merciful God,

Teach me how to take reproofs from friends,
   even though I think I do not deserve them;
Use them to make me tenderly afraid of sin,
   more jealous over myself,
   more concerned to keep heart and life
      unblameable;
Cause them to help me
   to reflect on my want of spirituality,
   to abhor myself,
   to look upon myself as unworthy,
   and make them beneficial to my soul.
May all your people know how little, mean,
     and vile I am,
   that they may see I am nothing,
   less than nothing,
   to be accounted nothing,
   that so they may pray for me aright,
   and have not the least dependence upon me.
It is sweet to be nothing and have nothing,
   and to be fed with crumbs from thy hands.
Blessed be thy Name for anything that life brings.
How do poor souls live who have not thee,
   or when helpless have no God to go to,
   who feel not the constraining force of thy love,
   and the sweetness of communion?
O how admirably dost thou captivate the soul,
   making all desires and affections centre on thee!
Give me such vivacity in religion,
   that I may be able to take all reproofs
     from other men
   as from thy hands,
   and glorify thee for them
   from a sense of thy beneficent love
   and of my need to have my pride destroyed.
</text>
		<searchtext>a prayer for correction o merciful god teach me how to take reproofs from friends even though i think i do not deserve them use them to make me tenderly afraid of sin more jealous over myself more concerned to keep heart and life unblameable cause them to help me to reflect on my want of spirituality to abhor myself to look upon myself as unworthy and make them beneficial to my soul may all your people know how little mean and vile i am that they may see i am nothing less than nothing to be accounted nothing that so they may pray for me aright and have not the least dependence upon me it is sweet to be nothing and have nothing and to be fed with crumbs from thy hands blessed be thy name for anything that life brings how do poor souls live who have not thee or when helpless have no god to go to who feel not the constraining force of thy love and the sweetness of communion o how admirably dost thou captivate the soul making all desires and affections centre on thee give me such vivacity in religion that i may be able to take all reproofs from other men as from thy hands and glorify thee for them from a sense of thy beneficent love and of my need to have my pride destroyed </searchtext>
		<primary>1</primary>
		<key>A</key>
		<time_signature></time_signature>
		<bpm></bpm>
		<tempo>Slow</tempo>
		<created>2010-08-12 00:26:22</created>
		<modified>2010-08-12 00:46:08</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<ccli></ccli>
		<album></album>
		<font_size>14</font_size>
	</Arrangement>
</data>

