<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<Song>
		<id>41478</id>
		<songbook_id>21</songbook_id>
		<title>It Is a Sword (Bloom)</title>
		<copyright>© Jon Bloom. All rights reserved. </copyright>
		<created>2011-07-01 10:57:45</created>
		<modified>2011-07-01 10:57:45</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<active>1</active>
		<ccli_required>0</ccli_required>
		<amazon_links></amazon_links>
	</Song>
	<Arrangement>
		<id>44599</id>
		<song_id>41478</song_id>
		<description>Initial arrangement</description>
		<text>
It is a sword, this word of God,
A weapon strong and good.
It has been forged by sovereign grace,
Prophetic fire and blood.
It's double-edged and there exists
No other blade so fine,
But skillful use is only learned
Through active use and time.

It is a sword with which to fight,
A sabre for the war,
For frequent are the battles and
Its use will bring its scar.
Designed as an offensive tool,
Not merely to defend,
Attack the enemy with it
And put him to an end!

And yet be warned!  This sword you wield
Becomes the Surgeon's knife
And ruthlessly reveals your sin;
It wounds to save your life.
It lives and acts and pierces deep,
A paradox indeed
The very sword that slays your foe
In mercy makes us bleed.

Grip tight the sword and keep it poised
When come the times of test.
Remain alert, its hilt in reach,
In times of peace and rest.
It is your hope, your confidence
When facing pain or strife;
Your guide, your strength, your faithful friend --
Indeed, it is your life! (Deut.32:47)
</text>
		<searchtext> it is a sword this word of god a weapon strong and good it has been forged by sovereign grace prophetic fire and blood its doubleedged and there exists no other blade so fine but skillful use is only learned through active use and time it is a sword with which to fight a sabre for the war for frequent are the battles and its use will bring its scar designed as an offensive tool not merely to defend attack the enemy with it and put him to an end and yet be warned this sword you wield becomes the surgeons knife and ruthlessly reveals your sin it wounds to save your life it lives and acts and pierces deep a paradox indeed the very sword that slays your foe in mercy makes us bleed grip tight the sword and keep it poised when come the times of test remain alert its hilt in reach in times of peace and rest it is your hope your confidence when facing pain or strife your guide your strength your faithful friend indeed it is your life deut3247 </searchtext>
		<primary>1</primary>
		<key>D</key>
		<time_signature></time_signature>
		<bpm></bpm>
		<tempo>Slow</tempo>
		<created>2011-07-01 10:57:45</created>
		<modified>2011-07-01 10:57:45</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<ccli></ccli>
		<album></album>
		<font_size>14</font_size>
	</Arrangement>
</data>

