<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<Song>
		<id>43244</id>
		<songbook_id>21</songbook_id>
		<title>Worthy of Affection</title>
		<copyright>Shane Barnard | Shane Everett © 2009 River Oaks Music Company | True Bliss Music | Waiting Room Music | Shane Everett Co-Pub Designee (a div. of EMI Christian Music Publishing)</copyright>
		<created>2011-11-02 01:28:34</created>
		<modified>2015-11-20 15:13:04</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<active>1</active>
		<ccli_required>0</ccli_required>
		<amazon_links></amazon_links>
	</Song>
	<Arrangement>
		<id>72326</id>
		<song_id>43244</song_id>
		<description>Drop Chorus to &quot;G&quot; at end</description>
		<text>Verse 1: 
[A/C#]   Deliverer You brought us out of the miry clay
[D2]   You set our feet upon the rock and You made us [A/C#]say 
Holy is the L[D2]ord
[A/C#]   We would declare Your thoughts about us and one by one
[D2]   It'd be too many to count so we simply c[A/C#]ome
And sing of Your great l[D2]ove
So we s[E]ing
We lift our hands and s[D2]ing

Chorus: 
You are w[A]orthy of affection
You're the r[D2]adiance of all of His glory
[A]   Let adoration fill this p[D2]lace
You hold [A]ev'rything together
By the W[D2]ord of Your immovable power
[A]   We sing a song of pr[D2]aise  [A    D2] 

[Repeat]      ([A]We sing) a song of pr[D]aise)   [A] 

Verse 2: 
[A/C#]   We are the broken down and we are the beaten up
[D2]   But what can stop us from a song of unending l[A/C#]ove
Holy is the L[D2]ord 
[A/C#]   You are the treasure the hope the bright and morning star
[D2]   You are the lover of our soul and You've won our h[A/C#]earts
We sing of Your great l[D2]ove
So we s[E]ing we lift our hands and s[D2]ing

{new_page}
BRIDGE: 
W[A]orthy are You L[D2]ord.   W[A]orthy are You L[D2]ord.
Oh w[A]orthy are You L[D2]ord.  W[A]orthy are You L[D2]ord of all my pr[A]aise.  [D2] 
All g[A/C#]lory to You L[D2]ord.  All g[A]lory to You L[D2]ord.
All g[A/C#]lory to You L[D2]ord.
Foreverm[A]ore,  Foreverm[D2]ore.

ENDING: 
H[A]oly are You L[D2]ord
H[A]oly are You L[D2]ord
Oh h[A]oly are You L[D2]ord

Chorus: 
You are w[A]orthy of affection
You're the r[D2]adiance of all of His glory
[A]   Let adoration fill this p[D2]lace
You hold [A]ev'rything together
By the W[D2]ord of Your immovable power
[A]   We sing a song of pr[D2]aise  [A    D2] 

[Repeat]      ([A]We sing) a song of pr[D]aise)   [A] 

{key:G}
Chorus: 
You are w[G]orthy of affection
You're the r[C2]adiance of all of His glory
[G]   Let adoration fill this p[C2]lace
You hold [G]ev'rything together
By the W[C2]ord of Your immovable power
[G]   We sing a song of pr[C2]aise  [G    C2] 

[Repeat]      ([G]We sing) a song of pr[C]aise)   [G] </text>
		<searchtext>verse 1 deliverer you brought us out of the miry clay you set our feet upon the rock and you made us say holy is the lord we would declare your thoughts about us and one by one itd be too many to count so we simply come and sing of your great love so we sing we lift our hands and sing chorus you are worthy of affection youre the radiance of all of his glory let adoration fill this place you hold evrything together by the word of your immovable power we sing a song of praise we sing a song of praise verse 2 we are the broken down and we are the beaten up but what can stop us from a song of unending love holy is the lord you are the treasure the hope the bright and morning star you are the lover of our soul and youve won our hearts we sing of your great love so we sing we lift our hands and sing bridge worthy are you lord worthy are you lord oh worthy are you lord worthy are you lord of all my praise all glory to you lord all glory to you lord all glory to you lord forevermore forevermore ending holy are you lord holy are you lord oh holy are you lord chorus you are worthy of affection youre the radiance of all of his glory let adoration fill this place you hold evrything together by the word of your immovable power we sing a song of praise we sing a song of praise chorus you are worthy of affection youre the radiance of all of his glory let adoration fill this place you hold evrything together by the word of your immovable power we sing a song of praise we sing a song of praise </searchtext>
		<primary>0</primary>
		<key>A</key>
		<time_signature>4/4</time_signature>
		<bpm>56</bpm>
		<tempo>Medium</tempo>
		<created>2015-11-20 15:05:16</created>
		<modified>2015-11-20 15:13:04</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<ccli>5627772</ccli>
		<album>LIft Up the Light</album>
		<font_size>14</font_size>
	</Arrangement>
	<Arrangement>
		<id>46558</id>
		<song_id>43244</song_id>
		<description>Initial arrangement</description>
		<text>Verse 1: 
[A/C#]   Deliverer You brought us out of the miry clay
[D2]   You set our feet upon the rock and You made us [A/C#]say 
Holy is the L[D2]ord
[A/C#]   We would declare Your thoughts about us and one by one
[D2]   It'd be too many to count so we simply c[A/C#]ome
And sing of Your great l[D2]ove
So we s[E]ing
We lift our hands and s[D2]ing

Chorus: 
You are w[A]orthy of affection
You're the r[D2]adiance of all of His glory
[A]   Let adoration fill this p[D2]lace
You hold [A]ev'rything together
By the W[D2]ord of Your immovable power
[A]   We sing a song of pr[D2]aise  [A    D2] 

[Repeat]      ([A]We sing) a song of pr[D]aise)   [A] 

Verse 2: 
[A/C#]   We are the broken down and we are the beaten up
[D2]   But what can stop us from a song of unending l[A/C#]ove
Holy is the L[D2]ord 
[A/C#]   You are the treasure the hope the bright and morning star
[D2]   You are the lover of our soul and You've won our h[A/C#]earts
We sing of Your great l[D2]ove
So we s[E]ing we lift our hands and s[D2]ing

{new_page}
BRIDGE: 
W[A]orthy are You L[D2]ord
W[A]orthy are You L[D2]ord
Oh w[A]orthy are You L[D2]ord
W[A]orthy are You L[D2]ord of all my pr[A]aise  [D2] 
All g[A/C#]lory to You L[D2]ord
All g[A]lory to You L[D2]ord
All g[A/C#]lory to You L[D2]ord
Foreverm[A]ore
Foreverm[D2]ore

ENDING: 
H[A]oly are You L[D2]ord
H[A]oly are You L[D2]ord
Oh h[A]oly are You L[D2]ord</text>
		<searchtext>verse 1 deliverer you brought us out of the miry clay you set our feet upon the rock and you made us say holy is the lord we would declare your thoughts about us and one by one itd be too many to count so we simply come and sing of your great love so we sing we lift our hands and sing chorus you are worthy of affection youre the radiance of all of his glory let adoration fill this place you hold evrything together by the word of your immovable power we sing a song of praise we sing a song of praise verse 2 we are the broken down and we are the beaten up but what can stop us from a song of unending love holy is the lord you are the treasure the hope the bright and morning star you are the lover of our soul and youve won our hearts we sing of your great love so we sing we lift our hands and sing bridge worthy are you lord worthy are you lord oh worthy are you lord worthy are you lord of all my praise all glory to you lord all glory to you lord all glory to you lord forevermore forevermore ending holy are you lord holy are you lord oh holy are you lord</searchtext>
		<primary>1</primary>
		<key>A</key>
		<time_signature>4/4</time_signature>
		<bpm>56</bpm>
		<tempo>Medium</tempo>
		<created>2011-11-02 01:28:34</created>
		<modified>2012-04-28 15:38:11</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<ccli>5627772</ccli>
		<album>LIft Up the Light</album>
		<font_size>14</font_size>
	</Arrangement>
</data>

