<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<Song>
		<id>60588</id>
		<songbook_id>21</songbook_id>
		<title>Grace Alone</title>
		<copyright>Dustin Kensrue © 2013 Dead Bird Theology (Admin. by Music Services, Inc.) It's All About Jesus Music (Admin. by Music Services, Inc.)</copyright>
		<created>2014-10-23 14:12:30</created>
		<modified>2014-10-25 19:57:01</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<active>1</active>
		<ccli_required>0</ccli_required>
		<amazon_links></amazon_links>
	</Song>
	<Arrangement>
		<id>66255</id>
		<song_id>60588</song_id>
		<description>Initial arrangement</description>
		<text>Intro: 
[|  G    |  G   |  C   |  C   |  G    |  G   |  C   |  C   |]


Verse 1: 
[G]I was an orphan, lost at the fall; 
Ru[C]nning away when I’d hear you call,
[G]    But Father, you worked your will. [C] 
[G]I had no righteousness of my own; 
I h[C]ad no right to draw near your throne,
[G]    But Father, you loved me still. [C] 

Chorus 1: 
And in [D]love, before you l[Em]aid the world’s found[C]ation, 
You pred[D]estined to a[Em]dopt me as your [C]own. 
You have [D]raised me up so [Em]high above my s[C]tation; 
I’m a c[D]hild of God by g[Em]race, and grace a[C]lone.


Interlude: 
[|  G    |  G   |  C   |  C   |  G    |  G   |  C   |  C   |]


Verse 2: 
[G]You left your home to seek out the lost; 
You [C]knew the great and terrible cost 
[G]    But Jesus, your face was set. [C] 
[G]I worked my fingers down to the bone; 
N[C]othing I did could ever atone, 
[G]    But Jesus, you paid my debt. [C] 

Chorus 2: 
By your b[D]lood I have re[Em]demption and salv[C]ation.
Lord you [D]died that I might r[Em]eap what you have s[C]own, 
And you r[D]ose that I might [Em]be a new cre[C]ation.
I am b[D]orn again by [Em]grace, and grace a[C]lone.

{new_page}
Bridge: 
[G/B]I was darkness all of my life, 
[C]I never knew the day from the night,
[D]    But Spirit, you [G/B]made me s[C]ee.
[G/B]I swore I knew the way on my own; 
[C]Head full of rocks, a heart made of stone
[D]    But Spirit, you [G/B]moved in [C]me.

Chorus 3: 
And at your t[G]ouch my sleeping spirit was awa[C]kened;
On my [Em]darkened heart the light of Christ has sh[C]one.
Called in[G]to a kingdom [Am]that cannot sh[C]aken;
Heaven’s [Em]citizen by g[D]race, and grace alon[C]e.

Tag: 
So I’ll s[D]tand in faith by gr[Em]ace, and grace alo[C]ne
I will [D]run the race by gr[Em]ace, and grace alo[C]ne
I will s[D]lay my sin by gr[Em]ace, and grace alo[C]ne
I will r[D]each the end by gr[Em]ace, and grace alo[C]ne</text>
		<searchtext>intro verse 1 i was an orphan lost at the fall running away when id hear you call but father you worked your will i had no righteousness of my own i had no right to draw near your throne but father you loved me still chorus 1 and in love before you laid the worlds foundation you predestined to adopt me as your own you have raised me up so high above my station im a child of god by grace and grace alone interlude verse 2 you left your home to seek out the lost you knew the great and terrible cost but jesus your face was set i worked my fingers down to the bone nothing i did could ever atone but jesus you paid my debt chorus 2 by your blood i have redemption and salvation lord you died that i might reap what you have sown and you rose that i might be a new creation i am born again by grace and grace alone bridge i was darkness all of my life i never knew the day from the night but spirit you made me see i swore i knew the way on my own head full of rocks a heart made of stone but spirit you moved in me chorus 3 and at your touch my sleeping spirit was awakened on my darkened heart the light of christ has shone called into a kingdom that cannot shaken heavens citizen by grace and grace alone tag so ill stand in faith by grace and grace alone i will run the race by grace and grace alone i will slay my sin by grace and grace alone i will reach the end by grace and grace alone</searchtext>
		<primary>1</primary>
		<key>G</key>
		<time_signature>4/4</time_signature>
		<bpm></bpm>
		<tempo>Fast</tempo>
		<created>2014-10-23 14:12:30</created>
		<modified>2014-10-25 19:57:01</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<ccli>7004659</ccli>
		<album>The Water and the Blood</album>
		<font_size>14</font_size>
	</Arrangement>
</data>

