<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<Song>
		<id>50502</id>
		<songbook_id>21</songbook_id>
		<title>Let All Mortal Flesh Keep Silence</title>
		<copyright>Liturgy of St. James, 4th Century; Translated from Greek to English by Gerard Moultrie, 1864.</copyright>
		<created>2012-12-01 14:34:34</created>
		<modified>2016-12-15 00:05:16</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<active>1</active>
		<ccli_required>0</ccli_required>
		<amazon_links></amazon_links>
	</Song>
	<Arrangement>
		<id>54641</id>
		<song_id>50502</song_id>
		<description>Initial arrangement</description>
		<text>Verse 1: 
[Dm]Let all mortal flesh keep s[C7]ilence,
[Dm/Bb]And with fear and trembling s[Am]tand;
[Dm]Ponder nothing earthly m[C7]inded,
[Dm/Bb]For with blessing in His h[Am]and,
[Dm]Christ our God to e[C]arth desc[Dm/Bb]end[C]eth,
[Dm]Our full homage [C]to d[Am7]em[Dm]and.

Verse 2: 
[Dm]King of kings, yet born of M[C7]ary,
[Dm/Bb]As of old on earth He st[Am]ood,
[Dm]Lord of lords, in human v[C7]esture,
[Dm/Bb]In the body and the bl[Am]ood;
[Dm]He will give to [C]all the f[Dm/Bb]aithf[C]ul
[Dm]His own self for h[C]eaven[Am7]ly f[Dm]ood.

{new_page}
Verse 3: 
[Dm]Rank on rank the host of h[C7]eaven
[Dm/Bb]Spreads its vanguard on the w[Am]ay,
[Dm]As the Light of light desc[C7]endeth
[Dm/Bb]From the realms of endless d[Am]ay,
[Dm]That the powers of h[C]ell may v[Dm/Bb]an[C]ish
[Dm]As the darkness cl[C]ears [Am7]aw[Dm]ay.

Verse 4: 
[Dm]At His feet the six winged s[C7]eraph,
[Dm/Bb]Cherubim with sleepless e[Am]ye,
[Dm]Veil their faces to the pr[C7]esence,
[Dm/Bb]As with ceaseless voice they c[Am]ry:
[Dm]Alleluia, [C]Allel[Dm/Bb]ui[C]a
[Dm]Alleluia, L[C]ord M[Am7]ost H[Dm]igh!


(4th Century)</text>
		<searchtext>verse 1 let all mortal flesh keep silence and with fear and trembling stand ponder nothing earthly minded for with blessing in his hand christ our god to earth descendeth our full homage to demand verse 2 king of kings yet born of mary as of old on earth he stood lord of lords in human vesture in the body and the blood he will give to all the faithful his own self for heavenly food verse 3 rank on rank the host of heaven spreads its vanguard on the way as the light of light descendeth from the realms of endless day that the powers of hell may vanish as the darkness clears away verse 4 at his feet the six winged seraph cherubim with sleepless eye veil their faces to the presence as with ceaseless voice they cry alleluia alleluia alleluia lord most high 4th century</searchtext>
		<primary>1</primary>
		<key>Dm</key>
		<time_signature>4/4</time_signature>
		<bpm></bpm>
		<tempo>Slow</tempo>
		<created>2012-12-01 14:34:34</created>
		<modified>2012-12-17 16:03:53</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<ccli></ccli>
		<album></album>
		<font_size>16</font_size>
	</Arrangement>
	<Arrangement>
		<id>76192</id>
		<song_id>50502</song_id>
		<description>With Responsive Reading</description>
		<text>Verse 1: 
[Dm]Let all mortal flesh keep s[C7]ilence,
[Dm/Bb]And with fear and trembling s[Am]tand;
[Dm]Ponder nothing earthly m[C7]inded,
[Dm/Bb]For with blessing in His h[Am]and,
[Dm]Christ our God to e[C]arth desc[Dm/Bb]end[C]eth,
[Dm]Our full homage [C]to d[Am7]em[Dm]and.

Verse 2: 
[Dm]King of kings, yet born of M[C7]ary,
[Dm/Bb]As of old on earth He st[Am]ood,
[Dm]Lord of lords, in human v[C7]esture,
[Dm/Bb]In the body and the bl[Am]ood;
[Dm]He will give to [C]all the f[Dm/Bb]aithf[C]ul
[Dm]His own self for h[C]eaven[Am7]ly f[Dm]ood.



Worship Leader:
In the beginning was the Word, 
     And the Word was with God, 
And the Word was God. 
     He was in the beginning with God. 
All things were made through him, 
     And without him was not any thing made 
     That was made. 
(John 1:1-3)


Congregation:
In him was life, and the life was the light of men. 
     The light shines in the darkness, 
And the darkness has not overcome it.
(John 1:4-5)

{new_page}
Verse 3: 
[Dm]Rank on rank the host of h[C7]eaven
[Dm/Bb]Spreads its vanguard on the w[Am]ay,
[Dm]As the Light of light desc[C7]endeth
[Dm/Bb]From the realms of endless d[Am]ay,
[Dm]That the powers of h[C]ell may v[Dm/Bb]an[C]ish
[Dm]As the darkness cl[C]ears [Am7]aw[Dm]ay.



Worship Leader:
And the Word became flesh and dwelt among us, 
     And we have seen his glory, 
Glory as of the only Son from the Father, 
     Full of grace and truth.
(John 1:14)


Congregation:
The LORD is in his holy temple;
     Let all the earth keep silence before him.”
(Habakkuk 2:20)


(4th Century)</text>
		<searchtext>verse 1 let all mortal flesh keep silence and with fear and trembling stand ponder nothing earthly minded for with blessing in his hand christ our god to earth descendeth our full homage to demand verse 2 king of kings yet born of mary as of old on earth he stood lord of lords in human vesture in the body and the blood he will give to all the faithful his own self for heavenly food worship leader in the beginning was the word and the word was with god and the word was god he was in the beginning with god all things were made through him and without him was not any thing made that was made john 113 congregation in him was life and the life was the light of men the light shines in the darkness and the darkness has not overcome it john 145 verse 3 rank on rank the host of heaven spreads its vanguard on the way as the light of light descendeth from the realms of endless day that the powers of hell may vanish as the darkness clears away worship leader and the word became flesh and dwelt among us and we have seen his glory glory as of the only son from the father full of grace and truth john 114 congregation the lord is in his holy temple let all the earth keep silence before him habakkuk 220 4th century</searchtext>
		<primary>0</primary>
		<key>Dm</key>
		<time_signature>4/4</time_signature>
		<bpm></bpm>
		<tempo>Slow</tempo>
		<created>2016-12-15 00:03:45</created>
		<modified>2016-12-15 00:05:16</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<ccli></ccli>
		<album></album>
		<font_size>15</font_size>
	</Arrangement>
</data>

