<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<Song>
		<id>33286</id>
		<songbook_id>21</songbook_id>
		<title>Indescribable</title>
		<copyright>Words and music by Laura Story (additional lyrics by Jesse Reeves, chorus 3 by Jon Bloom) © 2004 worshiptogether.com Songs/sixsteps Music/Gleaning Publishing (adm. By EMI Christian Music Publishing) Used by permission. All rights reserved.</copyright>
		<created>2010-03-27 17:17:18</created>
		<modified>2013-06-01 19:06:22</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<active>1</active>
		<ccli_required>0</ccli_required>
		<amazon_links></amazon_links>
	</Song>
	<Arrangement>
		<id>35537</id>
		<song_id>33286</song_id>
		<description>Initial arrangement</description>
		<text>VERSE 1: 
[Bm]From the highest of heights to the d[A/C#]epths of the s[D]ea 
[Em7]Creations revealing Your m[D]ajest[C]y   [C4]
[Bm]From the colors of Fall to the fr[A/C#]agrance of[D] Spring
[Em7]Ev’ry creature unique in the [G/D]song that it[C] sings
[G/B]All excl[A/C#]aiming


CHORUS: 
[D] Indescribable, [A] uncontainable
[G2]You placed the stars in the sky
And You know them by[Bm] name
[D/F#] You are amazing,[G] God
[D] All powerful, [A] untamable
[G]Awestruck, we fall to our knees as we humbly pr[Bm]oclaim
[D/F#]You are amazing,[G2] God


VERSE 2: 
[Bm] Who has told ev’ry lightning bolt w[A/C#]here it should[D] go
[Em7]Or seen heavenly storehouses l[D]aden with[C]snow?   [C4]
[Bm]Who imagined the sun and gives s[A/C#]ource to its[D] light
[Em7]Yet conceals it to bring us the c[G/D]oolness of[C] night?
[G/B]None can [A/C#]fathom

{new_page}
CHORUS 2: 
[D] Indescribable, [A] uncontainable
[G2]You placed the stars in the sky
And You know them by[Bm] name
[D/F#] You are amazing, [G] God
[D] Incomparable,[A] unchangeable
[G]You see the depths of my heart
And You love me the[Bm] same
[D/F#]You are amazing,[G2] God


CHORUS 3: 
[D] Unsurpassable, [A] all-merciful
[G2]You bore the guilt of my sin
And removed all my [Bm] shame
[D/F#]You are amazing, [G] God
[D] Indestructible, [A] undefeatable
[G]You destroyed death’s claim on me
When you conquered the [Bm] grave
[D/F#]You are amazing, [G2] God
</text>
		<searchtext>verse 1 from the highest of heights to the depths of the sea creations revealing your majesty from the colors of fall to the fragrance of spring evry creature unique in the song that it sings all exclaiming chorus indescribable uncontainable you placed the stars in the sky and you know them by name you are amazing god all powerful untamable awestruck we fall to our knees as we humbly proclaim you are amazing god verse 2 who has told evry lightning bolt where it should go or seen heavenly storehouses laden withsnow who imagined the sun and gives source to its light yet conceals it to bring us the coolness of night none can fathom chorus 2 indescribable uncontainable you placed the stars in the sky and you know them by name you are amazing god incomparable unchangeable you see the depths of my heart and you love me the same you are amazing god chorus 3 unsurpassable allmerciful you bore the guilt of my sin and removed all my shame you are amazing god indestructible undefeatable you destroyed deaths claim on me when you conquered the grave you are amazing god </searchtext>
		<primary>1</primary>
		<key>D</key>
		<time_signature>6/8</time_signature>
		<bpm></bpm>
		<tempo>Medium</tempo>
		<created>2010-03-27 17:17:18</created>
		<modified>2011-04-16 14:03:51</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<ccli></ccli>
		<album></album>
		<font_size>16</font_size>
	</Arrangement>
	<Arrangement>
		<id>58296</id>
		<song_id>33286</song_id>
		<description>Ps. 19 / Col 1 readings</description>
		<text>VERSE 1: 
[Bm]From the highest of heights to the d[A/C#]epths of the s[D]ea 
[Em7]Creations revealing Your m[D]ajest[C]y   [C4] 
[Bm]From the colors of Fall to the fr[A/C#]agrance of[D] Spring
[Em7]Ev’ry creature unique in the [G/D]song that it[C] sings
[G/B]All excl[A/C#]aiming


CHORUS: 
[D] Indescribable, [A] uncontainable
[G2]You placed the stars in the sky
And You know them by[Bm] name
[D/F#] You are amazing,[G] God
[D] All powerful, [A] untamable
[G]Awestruck, we fall to our knees as we humbly pr[Bm]oclaim
[D/F#]You are amazing,[G2] God

READING 1: 
[Bm]The heavens declare the glory of God,
and the [A/C#]sky above proclaims his [D]handiwork.
[Em7]Day to day pours out speech,
and [D]night to night reveals [C]knowledge.  [C4] 
[Bm]There is no speech, nor are there words,
whose [A/C#]voice is not he[D]ard.
[Em7]Their voice goes out through all the earth,
and their words to the [G/D]end of the wo[C]rld. [G/B     A/C#] 


[(Back to Chorus 1)]


{new_page}
VERSE 2: 
[Bm] Who has told ev’ry lightning bolt w[A/C#]here it should[D] go
[Em7]Or seen heavenly storehouses l[D]aden with[C]snow?   [C4] 
[Bm]Who imagined the sun and gives s[A/C#]ource to its[D] light
[Em7]Yet conceals it to bring us the c[G/D]oolness of[C] night?
[G/B]None can [A/C#]fathom

CHORUS 2: 
[D] Indescribable, [A] uncontainable
[G2]You placed the stars in the sky
And You know them by[Bm] name
[D/F#] You are amazing, [G] God
[D] Incomparable,[A] unchangeable
[G]You see the depths of my heart
And You love me the[Bm] same
[D/F#]You are amazing,[G2] God


{new_page}
READING 2: 
[Bm]JESUS is the image of the invisible God, 
       the [A/C#]firstborn of all cre[D]ation. 
[Em7] For by him all things were created, 
       in [D]heaven and on [C]earth, visible and invisible... 
[Bm]AND in him all the fullness of God was [A/C#]pleased to dw[D]ell, 
       and through him to reconcile to himself all 
t[Em7]hings, whether on earth or in heaven, making [C]peace 
       by the blood of his cro[G/B]ss.   [A/C#] 

CHORUS 3: 
[D] Unsurpassable, [A] all-merciful
[G2]You bore the guilt of my sin
And removed all my [Bm] shame
[D/F#]You are amazing, [G] God
[D] Indestructible, [A] undefeatable
[G]You destroyed death’s claim on me
When you conquered the [Bm] grave
[D/F#]You are amazing, [G2] God   [key change A   B] 

{key:E}
CHORUS 3: 
[E] Unsurpassable, [B] all-merciful
[A2]You bore the guilt of my sin
And removed all my [C#m] shame
[E/G#]You are amazing, [A] God
[E] Indestructible, [B] undefeatable
[A]You destroyed death’s claim on me
When you conquered the [C#m] grave
[E/G#]You are amazing, [A2] God</text>
		<searchtext>verse 1 from the highest of heights to the depths of the sea creations revealing your majesty from the colors of fall to the fragrance of spring evry creature unique in the song that it sings all exclaiming chorus indescribable uncontainable you placed the stars in the sky and you know them by name you are amazing god all powerful untamable awestruck we fall to our knees as we humbly proclaim you are amazing god reading 1 the heavens declare the glory of god and the sky above proclaims his handiwork day to day pours out speech and night to night reveals knowledge there is no speech nor are there words whose voice is not heard their voice goes out through all the earth and their words to the end of the world verse 2 who has told evry lightning bolt where it should go or seen heavenly storehouses laden withsnow who imagined the sun and gives source to its light yet conceals it to bring us the coolness of night none can fathom chorus 2 indescribable uncontainable you placed the stars in the sky and you know them by name you are amazing god incomparable unchangeable you see the depths of my heart and you love me the same you are amazing god reading 2 jesus is the image of the invisible god the firstborn of all creation for by him all things were created in heaven and on earth visible and invisible and in him all the fullness of god was pleased to dwell and through him to reconcile to himself all things whether on earth or in heaven making peace by the blood of his cross chorus 3 unsurpassable allmerciful you bore the guilt of my sin and removed all my shame you are amazing god indestructible undefeatable you destroyed deaths claim on me when you conquered the grave you are amazing god chorus 3 unsurpassable allmerciful you bore the guilt of my sin and removed all my shame you are amazing god indestructible undefeatable you destroyed deaths claim on me when you conquered the grave you are amazing god</searchtext>
		<primary>0</primary>
		<key>D</key>
		<time_signature>6/8</time_signature>
		<bpm></bpm>
		<tempo>Medium</tempo>
		<created>2013-06-01 19:02:50</created>
		<modified>2013-06-01 19:06:22</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<ccli></ccli>
		<album></album>
		<font_size>14</font_size>
	</Arrangement>
</data>

