<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<Song>
		<id>30145</id>
		<songbook_id>21</songbook_id>
		<title>Z - Valley of Vision Prayer: Confession and Petition</title>
		<copyright></copyright>
		<created>2009-10-16 11:45:34</created>
		<modified>2010-03-12 00:25:56</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<active>1</active>
		<ccli_required>0</ccli_required>
		<amazon_links></amazon_links>
	</Song>
	<Arrangement>
		<id>32097</id>
		<song_id>30145</song_id>
		<description>Initial arrangement</description>
		<text>Holy Lord, I have sinned times without number, 
    and been guilty of pride and unbelief.  
I have failed to find your mind in your Word, 
    and neglected to seek You in my daily life. 
My transgressions and short-comings present me with a list of accusations, 
    but I bless you that they will not stand against me, 
    for all have been laid on Christ. 
Go on to subdue my corruptions, 
    and grant me grace to live above them. 
Let not the passions of the flesh nor lusts of the mind 
    bring my spirit into subjection, 
    but, Lord, rule over me in liberty and power. 

I thank you that many of my prayers have been refused. 
I have asked wrongly and do not have, 
    I have prayed from lusts and been rejected, 
    I have longed for Egypt and been given a wilderness.
Go on with your patient work, answering 'no' to my wrongful prayers, 
    and fitting me to accept it.
Purge me from every false desire, every base aspiration, 
    everything contrary to your rule. 
I thank you for your wisdom and your love, 
    for all the acts of discipline to which I am subject, 
    for sometimes putting me into the furnace 
    to refine my gold and remove my dross. 

No trial is so hard to bear as a sense of sin. 
If you should give me choice to live in pleasure and keep my sins, 
    or to have them burnt away with trial, 
    give me sanctified affliction. 
Deliver me from every evil habit, 
    every accretion of former sins, 
    everything that dims the brightness of your grace in me, 
    everything that prevents me taking delight in you. 
Then I shall bless you, God of Jeshurun* 
    for helping me to be upright.


*Jeshurun means &quot;the upright one,&quot; another name for Israel. 
Adapted from &quot;Confession and Repentence&quot; at www.banneroftruth.org. 
 </text>
		<searchtext>holy lord i have sinned times without number and been guilty of pride and unbelief i have failed to find your mind in your word and neglected to seek you in my daily life my transgressions and shortcomings present me with a list of accusations but i bless you that they will not stand against me for all have been laid on christ go on to subdue my corruptions and grant me grace to live above them let not the passions of the flesh nor lusts of the mind bring my spirit into subjection but lord rule over me in liberty and power i thank you that many of my prayers have been refused i have asked wrongly and do not have i have prayed from lusts and been rejected i have longed for egypt and been given a wilderness go on with your patient work answering no to my wrongful prayers and fitting me to accept it purge me from every false desire every base aspiration everything contrary to your rule i thank you for your wisdom and your love for all the acts of discipline to which i am subject for sometimes putting me into the furnace to refine my gold and remove my dross no trial is so hard to bear as a sense of sin if you should give me choice to live in pleasure and keep my sins or to have them burnt away with trial give me sanctified affliction deliver me from every evil habit every accretion of former sins everything that dims the brightness of your grace in me everything that prevents me taking delight in you then i shall bless you god of jeshurun for helping me to be upright jeshurun means the upright one another name for israel adapted from confession and repentence at wwwbanneroftruthorg </searchtext>
		<primary>1</primary>
		<key>A</key>
		<time_signature></time_signature>
		<bpm></bpm>
		<tempo>Slow</tempo>
		<created>2009-10-16 11:45:34</created>
		<modified>2010-03-12 00:25:56</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<ccli></ccli>
		<album></album>
		<font_size>14</font_size>
	</Arrangement>
</data>

