<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<Song>
		<id>66004</id>
		<songbook_id>21</songbook_id>
		<title>Z - Luke 2:15-20 </title>
		<copyright></copyright>
		<created>2015-12-17 05:33:50</created>
		<modified>2015-12-17 05:33:50</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<active>1</active>
		<ccli_required>0</ccli_required>
		<amazon_links></amazon_links>
	</Song>
	<Arrangement>
		<id>72468</id>
		<song_id>66004</song_id>
		<description>Initial arrangement</description>
		<text>When the angels went away from them into heaven, 
the shepherds said to one another, 
“Let us go over to Bethlehem and see this thing that has happened,
 which the Lord has made known to us.” 
And they went with haste and found Mary and Joseph, 
and the baby lying in a manger. 
And when they saw it, they made known the saying 
that had been told them concerning this child. 
And all who heard it wondered at what the shepherds told them. 
But Mary treasured up all these things, pondering them in her heart. 
And the shepherds returned, glorifying and praising God 
for all they had heard and seen, as it had been told them.

(Luke 2:15-20 ESV)</text>
		<searchtext>when the angels went away from them into heaven the shepherds said to one another let us go over to bethlehem and see this thing that has happened which the lord has made known to us and they went with haste and found mary and joseph and the baby lying in a manger and when they saw it they made known the saying that had been told them concerning this child and all who heard it wondered at what the shepherds told them but mary treasured up all these things pondering them in her heart and the shepherds returned glorifying and praising god for all they had heard and seen as it had been told them luke 21520 esv</searchtext>
		<primary>1</primary>
		<key>A</key>
		<time_signature></time_signature>
		<bpm></bpm>
		<tempo>Slow</tempo>
		<created>2015-12-17 05:33:50</created>
		<modified>2015-12-17 05:33:50</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<ccli></ccli>
		<album></album>
		<font_size>14</font_size>
	</Arrangement>
</data>

