<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
	<Song>
		<id>35428</id>
		<songbook_id>21</songbook_id>
		<title>Z - Psalm 42:1-5</title>
		<copyright>English Standard Version</copyright>
		<created>2010-08-20 00:52:12</created>
		<modified>2010-08-20 00:52:12</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<active>1</active>
		<ccli_required>0</ccli_required>
		<amazon_links></amazon_links>
	</Song>
	<Arrangement>
		<id>37881</id>
		<song_id>35428</song_id>
		<description>Initial arrangement</description>
		<text>
Worship Team:
As a deer pants for flowing streams,
So pants my soul for you, O God.

Congregation:
My soul thirsts for God, for the living God.
When shall I come and appear before God?

Worship Team:
My tears have been my food day and night,
While they say to me all the day long,
“Where is your God?”

Congregation:
These things I remember, As I pour out my soul:
How I would go with the throng
And lead them in procession to the house of God
With glad shouts and songs of praise,
A multitude keeping festival.

Worship Team:
Why are you cast down, O my soul,
And why are you in turmoil within me?

Everyone:
Hope in God; for I shall again praise him,
my salvation and my God.</text>
		<searchtext> worship team as a deer pants for flowing streams so pants my soul for you o god congregation my soul thirsts for god for the living god when shall i come and appear before god worship team my tears have been my food day and night while they say to me all the day long where is your god congregation these things i remember as i pour out my soul how i would go with the throng and lead them in procession to the house of god with glad shouts and songs of praise a multitude keeping festival worship team why are you cast down o my soul and why are you in turmoil within me everyone hope in god for i shall again praise him my salvation and my god</searchtext>
		<primary>1</primary>
		<key>A</key>
		<time_signature></time_signature>
		<bpm></bpm>
		<tempo>Slow</tempo>
		<created>2010-08-20 00:52:13</created>
		<modified>2010-08-20 00:52:13</modified>
		<creator>1546</creator>
		<ccli></ccli>
		<album></album>
		<font_size>16</font_size>
	</Arrangement>
</data>

